{"items": [{"question": "the branch of dentistry dealing with the prevention and correction of irregular teeth", "answer": "orthodontics", "options": ["psychiatrist", "orthodontics", "neuralgia", "psychosis"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "sharp and paroxysmal pain along the course of a nerve.", "answer": "neuralgia", "options": ["psychosis", "neuralgia", "psychiatrist", "paediatrics"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "a mental disorder characterized by symptoms", "answer": "psychosis", "options": ["paediatrics", "psychiatrist", "geriatrics", "psychosis"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "a physician who practices branch of medicine dealing with the diagnosis and treatment of mental disorders", "answer": "psychiatrist", "options": ["psychiatrist", "geriatrics", "paediatrics", "psychologist"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "the branch of medicine concerned with the treatment of infants and children", "answer": "paediatrics", "options": ["psychoanalyst", "paediatrics", "geriatrics", "psychologist"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "branch of medical science that deals with diseases and problems specific to old people", "answer": "geriatrics", "options": ["psychoanalyst", "orthodontist", "psychologist", "geriatrics"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "a specialist in mental characteristics of a particular person", "answer": "psychologist", "options": ["psychologist", "psychoanalyst", "optometrist", "orthodontist"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a person trained to practice A set of techniques for exploring underlying motives and a method of treating various mental disorders based on the theories of Sigmund Freud", "answer": "psychoanalyst", "options": ["orthodontist", "optician", "optometrist", "psychoanalyst"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A dentist specializing in the prevention or correction of irregularities of the teeth", "answer": "orthodontist", "options": ["osteopath", "optometrist", "optician", "orthodontist"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A person skilled in testing for defects of vision in order to prescribe corrective glasses", "answer": "optometrist", "options": ["optician", "chiropractic", "optometrist", "osteopath"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "a person who makes or sells eyeglasses and", "answer": "optician", "options": ["chiropodist", "osteopath", "chiropractic", "optician"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A therapist who manipulates the skeleton and muscles", "answer": "osteopath", "options": ["chiropodist", "graphology", "chiropractic", "osteopath"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A method of treatment that manipulates body structures (especially the spine) to relieve low back pain or even headache or high blood pressure", "answer": "chiropractic", "options": ["chiropodist", "graphology", "gerontology", "chiropractic"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A specialist in care for the feet", "answer": "chiropodist", "options": ["graphology", "gerontology", "chiropodist", "psychosomatic"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "the study of handwriting", "answer": "graphology", "options": ["psychogenic", "graphology", "psychosomatic", "gerontology"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "the branch of science that deals with aging and the problems of aged persons.", "answer": "gerontology", "options": ["psychogenic", "gerontology", "psychosomatic", "psychotherapy"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "of or pertaining to a physical disorder that is caused by or notably influenced by emotional factors.", "answer": "psychosomatic", "options": ["psycho therapeutics", "psychogenic", "psychotherapy", "psychosomatic"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "having origin in the mind or in a mental condition or process", "answer": "psychogenic", "options": ["psychotherapy", "psycho therapeutics", "psychogenic", "orthodontics"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "the treatment of psychological disorders or maladjustment by a professional technique", "answer": "psychotherapy", "options": ["psycho therapeutics", "orthodontics", "neuralgia", "psychotherapy"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "relating to or practicing treatment of mental and emotional disorders", "answer": "psycho therapeutics", "options": ["neuralgia", "orthodontics", "psycho therapeutics", "psychosis"], "answer_index": 3}], "title": "Session 6 to 8.txt", "total": 20}